Srijana Maharjan

Female

Sydney, Australia

srizana.m@gmail.com

https://srijanamaharjan.github.io/

I started programming in high school and have done several projects since then in PHP, JAVA and Android. I worked at Augusta Information Solutions as PHP developer for one and a half years as junior Web developer and at Woxweb IT Factory for 1 year and 10 months as Web developer developing WordPress plugins and customizing themes and web applications using custom PHP. After moving to Sydney, i continued working in WordPress at The Intermedia Group as a contractor for a month. I have been working at Brightside, an insurance company for over a year now as a fullstack developer using PHP, JavaScript, HTML, MySQL, GIT, AWS, Machine learning, ElasticSearch and more.

Skills

Programming Languages: JAVA, PHP

Databases: MSSQL, MySQL, Oracle

Tools: Phpstorm, Eclipse, Netbeans, Sublime Text, GIT, SVN, Adobe Photoshop

Others: Web Development (Javascript, HTML, CSS,JSP, WordPress, LESS, jQUery, AJAX,

Typescript), AngularJS, AWS

Experience

Apr2017 - current

Brightside - Developer (Full Time)

Working as a part of inhouse IT team developing solutions for the business that over 200 people use across 7 countries using mainly PHP, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL and cloud platforms.

Mar2017 - Apr2017

The Intermedia Group - Web Developer (Full Time)

Worked with members of the Digital team bridging the gap between graphical design and technical implementation producing, modifying, and maintaining web solutions using technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, PHP, WordPress, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

APR 2015 - JAN 2017

Woxweb IT Factory - Web Developer (Full Time)

Worked as a mid-level Web Developer monitoring junior developers, and debugging, developing, maintaining web solutions using PHP,JAVA, HTML5. CSS3, Angularjs, jQuery, LESS, Bootstrap, WordPress, MySQL and Javascript.

Projects

A. The University of Texas Medical School at Houston

Project Description: Online distribution of website content and web-based applications for complex large departments and school, including, but not limited to creating and implementing website content and web- or computer-based systems.

Responsibilities: Develop the website with the use of WordPress Custom post Types to create menu.

Used: PHP, WordPress ,SublimeText ,LESS, GIT, CPT

B. Lalitpur District Court

Project Description: A website for the district court of lalitpur for lawyers to share, communicate and collaborate information.

Responsibilities: Develop the website, support and training to users.

Used: PHP, WordPress, SublimeText

C. Wisefemales

Project Description: An online magazine with online store and discussion forums.

Responsibilities: Develop the website using WordPress and build custom plugins.

Used: PHP, WordPress, SublimeText

D. This world music

Project Description: A site for promotion of African traditional music with music mixers and online store

Responsibilities: Develop the website in WordPress and the music mixers using HTML5

Used: PHP, WordPress, SublimeText, HTML5

E. Setxmarketing

Project Description: A website for liquor promotion business with representative portal.

Responsibilities: Develop the website in WordPress and custom tools for exporting tasting reports.

Used: PHP, WordPress, SublimeText

SEP 2013- MAR 2015

Augusta Information Solutions- Web Developer (Full time)

Worked as junior Web developer with involvement on big projects such as Online Examination System using technologies like PHP,JAVA, JSP, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, MySQL.

Projects

A. Online Examination System

Project Description: An Online Examination System for Lucky Education Center that helps conduct academic examinations.

Responsibilities: Develop models and views for different user roles and user management module.

Used: PHP, Eclipse, SVN, MySQL

B. NamasteService

Project Description: Online shopping store with integrated payment gateways

Responsibilities: Develop the front-end and modules for integration of facebook, mailchimp widgets.

Used: PHP, jQuery, Eclipse, SVN, MySQL

Education

SEP 2013 - JAN 2017

University of Central Lancashire - BSc (Hons) Business Computing and Information System

2010 - 2013

Golden Gate Higher Sec School- High School